DESIGN STRENGTHS

I am passionate about design and especially the user-centered design process. My experience as an Industrial Designer taught me how to recognize interactions that can be improved, and design improved interactions within technical constraints. I also learned to work iteratively using user feedback to improve a product. My experience designing software has taught me to think systematically and to test and measure the success of new designs.



DESIGN SKILLS

Drocoss Skills

FIOCESS SKIIIS		recrifical skills
Hand Sketching		Adobe CC
User Flow Charts	CONFIDENT	Microsoft Office
Wireframing		Jutinmind Prototyper
Presentation Skills		Sketch
Persona Development	COMFORTABLE	InvisionApp
Storyboarding		Origami
User Research	FARMULAD	HTML & CSS

FAMILIAR

RECOGNITIONS

Usability Testing



2015 Engineering and Product Design Conference.

My paper, "The Sharing Economy and Design," was accepted, and I plan to present it in September 2015. Loughborrough, England.



2013-2015 Industrial Design Scholarship

In both my Junior and Senior years, the professors awarded me a scholarhip for exceptional work. Provo, Utah.

LANGUAGE SKILLS









Tachnical Skills

EDUCATION

From September 2009 to April 2015

BFA in Industrial Design.

Brigham Young University - Provo, Utah.

From January 2015 to April 2015

UX Design Apprenticeship on development of learning simulation software. Professor Derek Hansen, Brigham Young University - Provo.

From September 2014 to April 2015

Design Research Assistant on "Fragrance and Color" study. Professor Bryan Howell, Brigham Young University - Provo, Utah.

From August 2013 to September 2013

International Study Abroad.

Milan, Italy; Paris, France; London, England.

From June 2010 to June 2012 Service Mission.

Kyiv, Ukraine.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Part-Time Design Positions Brigham Young Univerity

Full-Time Internships Whirlpool, Fahrenheit Design

ID INTERN - FAHRENHEIT DESIGN

lune 2014 - September 2014

Worked closely with the Dell Enterprise designers, other smaller clients, and internal projects. Austin, Texas.

ID INTERN - WHIRLPOOL ADVANCED DESIGN STUDIO Ianuary 2014 - June 2014 Involved in all parts of design process as the only intern on the advanced design team.

Chicago, Illinois.

June 2013 - January 2013 Created marketing material for print, web, social media, and branding installations. Provo, Utah.

UI/UX DESIGNER - CENTER FOR TEACHING AND LEARNING June 2012 - April 2013 Designed new features and UI elements for the "Learning Suite" academic software. Provo, Utah.

HOBBIES & INTERESTS







GRAPHIC DESIGNER - BYLL ATHLETIC DEPARTMENT















